CURRICULUM VITAE

PERSONAL DATA



Karlina Ekawati Kartoredjo Female.Married.Moslem. Bandung,2 January 1980 Mobile : 0821 13331841/ 0818 690682

Home Phone: 021 850 2109
Email: lina_kartoredjo@yahoo.com
Address: Jl. Majalah - Kartini II no.45,Komplek
PWI,Cipinang Jak Tim

PERSONALITY

Self motivator, initiative, creative, hardworker, fast learner, able to work under pressure, high eagerness to learn new things, sociable and adaptable.

HIGHLIGHT

Interested in marketing, communication, branding, promotion, media and event management. 6 years experienced in Business Development for Content Provider and Telecommunication. Also have a working experience in one of woman's media advertising department.

And also 3 years have an experience in digital advertising development.

Motivation: expand knowledge, skills and experience by joining dynamic and creative team in a wellknowned company.

EDUCATION

1986-1992 : SD Cendrawasih II Jakarta 1992-1995 : SMP 12 Jakarta

1995-1998 : SMU Muhammadiyah 3 Jakarta

1998-2006: Univ. Prof.Dr.Moestopo Majoring Communication

WORKING EXPERIENCE

- ♣ Sr. Business Development at PT KI89 2014-Present Responsibilities:
- 1. Develop new programs and managing program budget.
- 2. Ensure identification, planning and execution of all / projects / Campaigns
 - 3. Work closely with business partners and all Operators (Telkomsel,XL,Indosat)
- 4. Work closely with vendors to doing all of program campaign (Mobile Advertising, Mobile Network, Social Media) based on period, cpc, cpm,cpa buying system.
 - 5. Able to analyze, monitoring and evaluate effectiveness of each project
 - 6. To be responsible for generating monthly marketing reports to Management for review
 - 7. Develop new program and managing each project
 - 8. Monitoring all of the program and make sure that everything is running well.
 - 9. To be responsible to get the revenue based on the KPI on every month.

WORKING EXPERIENCE

- Sr. Digital Account Manager at PT. MPG Indonesia (MPG) 2012- 2014 Responsibilities:
 - 1. Maintain & Service Client (Danone Group, Sari Husada, Kalbe, Indofood)
- 2.Ensure identification, planning, execution, monitoring, and reporting of all of projects / campaigns
 3.Able to analyze and evaluate effectiveness of each project
 - 4.To be Responsible for generating KPI's of client's campaign.
 - 5. Develop campaign program and managing each project on digital.
 - 6. To be responsible for every step of client's campaign (Material, deadline, launching program, monitoring, reporting).
- 7. Responsible for making a new concept to build brand awareness for a new brand in order to winning pitching of a new brand.

WORKING EXPERIENCE

- ♣ Business Development Manager at PT. Zalora Indonesia (Zalora) 2011- 2012

 Responsibilities:
 - 1. To be responsible to build brand awareness o the brand
 - 2. Responsible to make a concept how to increase sales on every month
 - 3. Ensure identification, planning, execution, monitoring, and reporting of all of projects / campaigns
 - 4. Able to analyze and evaluate effectiveness of each project
 - 5. To be responsible for generating KPI on revenue
 - 6. Develop campaign program and managing each project.
 - 7. Work closely with partner amd media (Telco's, Print Media, TVC, Radio, Portal Media & Digital Media

WORKING EXPERIENCE

- Telco Relation Manager at PT.Intertech Persada Media, Jakarta (Synergia Mobile) 2010 2012 Responsibilities:
 - 1. Develop promotion programs and managing program budget.
 - 2. Ensure identification, planning and execution of all / projects / campaigns
 - 3. Work closely with business partners and all Operators in Indonesia (Telkomsel,XL,Indosat,Axis,Three,SmartFren,Esia,Flexi)
 - 4. Able to analyze and evaluate effectiveness of each project
 - 5.Responsibilities for Generating monthly marketing reports to Management for review
 - 6.Develop promotion program and managing each project

WORKING EXPERIENCE

- Business Development at PT. Media Kreasindo Utama (Zing Mobile) 2009 2010 Responsibilities:
 - 1. Develop promotion programs and managing program budget.
 - 2. Ensure identification, planning and execution of all / projects / campaigns
 - 3. Work closely with business partners and all Operators in Indonesia (Telkomsel,XL,Indosat,Axis,Three,SmartFren,Esia,Flexi)
 - 4. Able to analyze and evaluate effectiveness of each project
 - 5.To be responsible for generating monthly marketing reports to management for review
 - 6.Develop promotion program and managing each project

WORKING EXPERIENCE

- Sr. Account Executive at Elle Indonesia Magazine 2006 2009 Responsibilities:
- 1. To be responsibilities to generate revenue from selling the advertisement pages.
 - 2. Work closely with clients
 - 3. Maintaining and always have to find new client